good evening!
Oh, a photographer's talk.
We have four minutes left.
I'm going to show you a recap of yesterday's first day and the second day.
I'll show you a quick recap of day 1 and day 2.
Hey, big brother.
Today, I went to buy the collaboration outfit that Akarin showed me the other day.
I went to buy it right away.
Isn't it time?
No, I've got plenty of time.
You can start now.
Okay, let's go for it.
Good work, sir.
Okay, let's get started.
Hello. Thank you very much.
Here we go again.
Hey, why did you write that you're Yuki's official boyfriend?
I was hoping you'd buy it.
You mean you want me to write it before they buy it?
Yes, that's right.
Ha-ha-ha.
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you? That's very nice to meet you. Thank you very much.
What, today? You live here?
Thank you for that.
Thank you for coming all the way from Oshima.
I'm glad you came all the way from Oshima.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Wow, did you hear this?
You can turn on YouTube.
They say I look better than I did an hour ago.
Oh, Mion's smiling.
What? What is it?
Are you happy? Thank you.
I'm so happy. Can I have some more?That's great. Can I have some more?
Yeah. How do you feel now?
I love you.
Ha-ha-ha.
Thank you.
You're the best and the most energetic fan.
Oh, Taiwan.
Wow, thank you!
Wow, Koyohong!
I said "chan".
Thank you, Doctor. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming from Taiwan.
Ah, Annyeong!
YouTube
A fan from Korea.
Annyong, you're so cute!
Let's make her a teammate.
That's possible.
No way. That's not possible.
I'd love to go to Korea, too.
Wait for me.
Thank you.
Wow, thank you. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy. I kind of want you to go.
Oh, really?
That's sweet.
Thank you. I'll do my best.
Oh, Yaso.
A Muscle fan.
Hey, uh...
Shouldn't we read A Muscle?
You should? You don't have to.
I'll read the book I sent you and then I'll...
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
I'm too lazy to read it.I'm too wasted to read it.
It's propped up in front of the TV.
But I'll read it now.
You're right.
Thank you very much.
I often watch your videos.
You do?
I went to your concert the other day, too, and it was a lot of fun.
You look like you're having a great time.
Saraba's YouTube is really interesting.
Do you have a favorite?
I think it's from the video graduation book.
Oh, it's great!
I've been told.
But I can't respond.
It's great.
Saraba's fans are here!
Hey there!
This is Mr. Saraba.
You saw him in the last video, right?
I did.
Hey, Ms. Koko!
You found me before I made my debut.
How are you doing lately?
Not so good.
What? Why? Because it's hot?
Yeah, but they came out for lunch.
Wow.
Boom!
Mmm-hmm.
Puppy dog Bong, why is this guy...
I'll use it!
That's enough for now.
You can talk normally now.
I'm so nervous!
I want you to use this much.I want you to use this much, after all.
I told him I was on YouTube.
I said, "What are you thinking about?" I got nervous and my stomach started to hurt.
You've known each other for 17 years.
I'm glad.
Thank you for everything.
Okay, I'll stop here.
That youtube video you did before.
I made a video like a weird fan who came to the handshake event.
He said something like this to me.
He said something like "stay beautiful forever" and you remember how angry he was?
And today, that person came to me.
After that, he said he thought about it.
Thank you for always being beautiful.
She thought about it a lot, rephrased it, and came all the way over here.
I felt bad. I really did.
I'm sorry, just a little bit.
That's all I wanted to say.
I'll be shaking hands with you again tomorrow.
I'll take pictures of tomorrow's event after I do some more.
I'll see you all tomorrow.
I'll do my best for the rest of the day.
Thank you for your patience.
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you! Thank you very much!
YouTube.
Are you watching? I'm glad you do.
Mr. Azoi.
Sorry about the name.
Mr. S. is very popular.
Can I show you that T-shirt?
This T-shirt is so lame.
It's official, right?
You can't wear that on a regular day, can you?
Absolutely.
Thanks for the center.Thank you for the center
Stylish
Thank you.
He's got a Ramune in the bottom.
It's cute.
Really?
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
I'm so happy about the cosmetics.
In the meantime, I'm going on a solo tour with Nana-chan.
Mr. Cafe Dash
I was so impressed by her singing.
It was so good!
I had to go tell her today.
Thank you so much!
I've loved you since I was a nervous wreck.
You were so sweet.
I was so nervous.
Everyone was like Aachan.
But you were so nice to me.
Thank you so much.
Nice to meet you.
I'm so happy to meet you.
Merry Christmas to the new Twitter!
I'm starting work again the day after tomorrow.
I'll be cheering you on.
Good luck!
I'll be rooting for you.
Comment before Corona
It's been about 3 years
Costume
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Go to the 100 yen store.
They have all the characters.
Want to go?You want to go there?
He recommended a 100-yen store.
Hello.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're here.
Is that it for today?
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work. Eight and a half hours of rest.
I'm going to eat. There's a little girl, about two years old.
I've been seeing her online for a long time, but this is the first time I've seen her in person. She's been looking at me like this the whole time.
She's been looking at me like this.
She's been looking at me like this the whole time.
I got really excited with a fan who said she's watching youtube of "Saraba".
Please tell me you like it... it was great!
I thought, "What if people who like the idol Kashiwa Yuki Yuki go to Saraba's live show?
But after a day or so, I found that there were no people who liked Yukirin Kashiwa and no people who disliked Yukirin Saraba.
No one likes or dislikes either of them.
Photo album
The photo album was really good!
Thank you so much!
I've only seen the pictures that are in the book.
I'm glad.
Please put the details here in the ticker
Please.
First time?
It's my first time... to have my first photo book.
My first photo book.
It's coming out July 20th.
What do you think?
It's coming out soon, and I've already chosen a title.
What's so exciting?
I didn't know that.
What does that mean?
Oh, I don't know.
I liked what you meant.I'm glad you meant well.
Yes, it was.
It makes me nervous.
You're making me nervous.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a lot of fun.
Please watch.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you very much for your hard work. It's over. Today was the first time in 3 or 4 years.
Some came all the way from overseas, and some came for the first time after seeing us on YouTube.
We are also doing an online chat session for those of you who are interested.
If you are interested in our new songs, you can sign up in advance, so please come and visit us.
That's all for now, I'm Koshi Engeki, a.k.a. Pucillin. See you soon!